I still love you unconscious
My dearest
Shiroku somaru sekai iro
The world's color turns white
Ushinatta mono chirabaru
As that which I lost now scatters
Koe ga shinzou megutte kareta kokoro ni ochita
A voice flows in my heart and falls on my withered soul
Sore wa kanashimi no neiro
Its timbre​ is one of sorrow
Suterareteyuku hikari usureyuku negai
The light is being discarded, its wish fading
Asu wo nozomu koto sae yurusarezu ni
Being allowed no hope for tomorrow
Omoidasu kage ni namida otoshita
As my tears fall in the shadows of these memories
Kasaneta te kara tsutawaru nukumori wo daite
I embrace the warmth conveyed by our superposed hands
Ai no imi sae wakarazu ni
Without even knowing the meaning of love
Mata sotto yorisoi nagara
And as I gently snuggle up to you again
Kimi wo tashika ni kanjiru ima wo hiroiatsumeru
I pick up all the moments where I'm certain I can feel you
I still love you unconscious
My Dearest (feel it even if I lose it)
My dearest (Feel it even if I lose it)
Fate is not a simulation (Tears remember)
My dearest