Rain on a sunny day
Out here in outer space
In a tangled web, many vows are said in this universe
Crossing the veil of night, beyond the speed of light
Can future science become supernatural?
And in a blink of an eye you and I, cast adrift in this quiet expanse
Nothing but consciousness, we're terrified and alone, far from home
And as our bodies dissolve into dust
Our life's purpose is over and done
Now countless particles and pixels journey on
Travel on toward tomorrow's universe
Here in the solar dance we spin, setting to pre-delete, meta-reference
Understanding is beyond our reach forever, we're seeking intervention
Space and time, putting it all on the line—ENIAC
Time's arrow isn't hitting its chosen target, lost in chaos, failing from the start
As billions of processes align, parallelism
Should we never learn to rewrite our future history—
Game over