Guru guru to henka suru sekai jousei no touhou
Times are changing, swirling all around these eastern lands
Toaru kankatsu achira kochira to
Near and far, a certain jurisdiction's in our hands
Koko demo guruguru
Back and forth, even swirling here around our band
Yume toka kibou ga kanashii toki ni wa
When your hopes and dreams crumble to dust
Hitogoe okake kudasai
Give us a call—you can count on us!
Roppouzensho mo chotto wa shitteru
And we happen to know a bit about the Six Codes
Dance no kime wa itsumo no keirei
So now we dance for you in our usual salute pose!
Seigi no mikata sono shoutai wa
As true heroes of justice, we hear your calls!
Cyber Force Dolls
That's right, we're the Cyber Force Dolls!
Smile is idol kirakira todokemasu
Smiles make idols, we'll shower you in radiance
Shoushin shoumei no keikan nano de arimasu
We're the real deal officers, never idle!
Itsudemo doko he demo
Any time, we'll run a trace
Anata no moto he shutsudou shimasu
And for you, put baddies in their place
Password ni wa oomoji komoji to
So don't forget: Uppercase, lowercase, symbols
Kigou wo ireyou
In my password phrase!
Seifu kokusai senroppyakusanjuu chou
1.63 quadrillion in debt:
Ougonhi no algorythm
An algorithm of the golden ratio
Osoru nakare deep learning
Be not afraid, deep learning is here to cure our woes
Inflation ritsu wa two point two no tomari
GDP going wild, inflation sitting at 2.2 percent
Hari no ana mo nerau mama ni
Taking aim for the eye of a needle
Araburu you haneru GDP
It's all being spent
Yume ni egaita sekai seifuku
The dream is now drawn, the world domination of us all...
Sore naraba
If for this, there is no mend...
Douzo hayame ni oosame kudasai
Then please, go ahead, bring it all to an end
Kami ni natta keshiki wa ikaga desu ka?
Let us know of the Godlike scenery above
Tomaranai anata ni atteta negau wa inori
Without stop, these hopes are our prayers to You
Arigataki mikotoba subete no mob he
Thankful words of the Lord, to every NPC
Server ochiru mae ni asu mo douka kami yo
We ask of You, God, before the server crash of tomorrow