Changes in current events swirling about in these eastern lands
That certain jurisdiction of near and far is now in our hands
Swirling about even here among our amazing band
When your hopes and dreams crumble to dust
Give us a call—you can always count on us!
Not to mention we happen to know a bit about the Six Codes
So now we dance our usual salute and meet you in this pose!
As the true heroes of justice, we hear your calls!
From: that's right, we, the Cyber Force Dolls!
Smiles make idols, we'll shower you all in radiance
We're the real deal officers, never idle!
Any time, we'll run a trace
And for you, put those baddies in their place
So don't forget: Uppercase, Lowercase, Symbols
In My Password Phrase!